anyhow5.com 2006-11-04

# Arts and Crafts - Privacy policy: anyhow5.com

We take your right to privacy very seriously.  
Anyhow5.com will not sell, transfer, assign or rent our customer or user information to any third party.

Personal information

You can visit anyhow5 website without telling us who you are and without giving any personal information about yourself.

Contact Information 

We can obtain access to your name, e-mail address and other contact information only when you become an customer with anyhow5, provide comments, or request information from anyhow5 and provide your name or return contact information.  
Contact information provided in connection with problems, comments or requests is used only to respond to those problems, comments or requests.  

Links to non-anyhow5 Web sites 

anyhow5 Web sites may contain links to other Web sites. anyhow5 is not responsible for the privacy policy practices or the content of those other Web sites.  
If you request something from anyhow5 Web site, for example, a product or a callback we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. 

Types of Information Collected

When you complete our form,(when you buy products) you send us your personal information including your name and address.

What type of information we colect when you browse our site

When you browse our website we not colect any type of information about you.

Providing information to us

When you use our website, you may choose to contact us by sending us an email using our Contact Us page. We will use your email address to respond to your query. We may also keep a note of your query ( ofline, not online) to help us improve the website.

Privacy Questions

If you have a question about this privacy policy, you can send an email to the anyhow5 webmaster. The address for this is monicajeleriu@anyhow5.com. 

How can I access or correct any personally identifying information about me?

To request a copy of the personally identifiable information you have sent to anyhow5, please send an e-mail containing your request to monicajeleriu@anyhow5.com. You must provide your full name and the e-mail from which the request is received (and to which the response will be sent). You may then correct or delete such information using the procedures specified in the e-mail. 

Notification of Changes 

This privacy policy was last updated on January 7, 2003. A notice will be posted on our website home page for 30 days if we change our privacy.
